Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 79, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Management of Personnel Quarterly, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 54)
- Box: 79, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The Case for Free Collective Bargaining, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 55)
    Author: Earl R. Bramblett
- Box: 79, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: The Organization of General Motors Corporation, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 56)
    Author: William M. Collins
- Box: 79, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: The Development and Growth of General Motors, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 57)
    Author: Harlow H. Curtice
- Box: 79, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Fortune: How Harlow Curtice Earns His $750,000, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 58)
    Author: Robert Sheehan
- Box: 79, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: GM Bets Billion No Slump, 1954; Publication (Box 79, Folder 59)
- Box: 79, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Information Handbook: A Reference for Press Radio Television, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 60)
- Box: 79, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Your GM Savings - Stock Purchase Program, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 61)
- Box: 79, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Central Personnel Department Organizational Chart, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 62)
- Box: 79, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Imperial Chemical Industries Limited Organization Chart, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 63)
- Box: 79, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Outline of Scheme of Assistance to Transferred Married Male Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 64)
- Box: 79, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Company's Grading Scheme for Tradesmen: Complete Operating Instructions, 1955; Publication (Box 79, Folder 65)
- Box: 79, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: I.C.I. Sickness Benefit Scheme, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 66)
- Box: 79, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Education and Training Activities Within I.C.I., 1953; Publication (Box 79, Folder 67)
    Author: F.H. Perkins
- Box: 79, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Promotions - Boiler Operations, 1951; Publication (Box 79, Folder 68)
- Box: 79, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: The Transport & General Workers' Union: "Nitro-Chalk" Plant - Manning, 1951; Publication (Box 79, Folder 69)
- Box: 79, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Supervisors' Training Course, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 70)
    Author: R.T. Wilson
- Box: 79, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Workers' Pension Fund, 1952; Publication (Box 79, Folder 71)
    Author: J.A.L. Young
- Box: 79, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 79, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Understanding Between the Company and the Undernoted Trade Unions Concerning the Position of Assistant Foremen, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 72)
- Box: 79, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the Chrysler Corporation - UAW Settlement: Economic Settlement, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 73)
- Box: 79, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 79, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Manual for Management Development, 1960; Publication (Box 79, Folder 74)
- Box: 79, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 79, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology: Chrysler Corporation 1939-64, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 75)
- Box: 79, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 79, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Alcoholism or Problem Drinking: Manual for Supervisors, 1976; Publication (Box 79, Folder 76)
- Box: 79, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 79, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 77)
- Box: 79, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 79, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Principles Governing the Development and Maintenance of a Salary Structure for Evaluated Positions, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 78)
    Author: M.G. de Jersey
- Box: 79, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 79, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Organization Chart, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 79)
- Box: 79, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 79, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Rules: Union - Management Co-operative Movement: Equipment Department, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 80)
- Box: 79, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 79, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Memorandum to Headquarters Examiners, 1955; Publication (Box 79, Folder 81)
    Author: R.C. Johnston
- Box: 79, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 79, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Basic Organization Chart, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 82)
- Box: 79, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 79, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: How to Run the Finances of a Railroad - and How Not to Run Them, 1952; Publication (Box 79, Folder 83)
    Author: Robert R. Young
- Box: 79, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 79, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Plan, 1975; Publication (Box 79, Folder 84)
- Box: 79, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 79, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: C&O-B&O Salary Administration Program, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 85)
- Box: 79, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 79, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Vacation Policy, 1969; Publication (Box 79, Folder 86)
  - Item 2: Military Leave Policy, 1969; Publication (Box 79, Folder 86)
- Box: 79, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 79, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: C&O/B&O Salary Administration Program, 1969; Publication (Box 79, Folder 87)
- Box: 79, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 79, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Your Future with the C&O/B&O Railroads, 1969; Publication (Box 79, Folder 88)
- Box: 79, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 79, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Chessie News: For the Whole C and O Family, 1958; Publication (Box 79, Folder 89)
- Box: 79, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 79, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Letter to Dr. Frederick Harbison, 1958; Publication (Box 79, Folder 90)
    Author: Frank J. Householder, Jr.
    Notes: April 9, 1958
- Box: 79, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 79, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Stock Option Incentive Plan: Statement of Purpose, 1951; Publication (Box 79, Folder 91)
    Notes: January 9, 1951
- Box: 79, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 79, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policy Manual, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 92)
- Box: 79, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 79, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan of the C&O/B&O Railroads, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 93)
- Box: 79, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 79, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Medical Benefits Plan, 1975; Publication (Box 79, Folder 94)
- Box: 79, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 79, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake & Ohio Supplemental Pension Plan, 1975; Publication (Box 79, Folder 95)
- Box: 79, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 79, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Baltimore & Ohio Supplemental Pension Plan, 1975; Publication (Box 79, Folder 96)
- Box: 79, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 79, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Baltimore & Ohio Supplemental Pension Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 97)
- Box: 79, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 79, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Your Guide to the Employees Stock Purchase Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 79, Folder 98)
- Box: 80, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Education and Training: Unit 364, Harvester Central School, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Box: 80, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Education and Training: Job Instructor Training Course, 1951; Publication (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Author: L.N. Carey
  - Item 2: Longer Life for Cutting Tools, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Notes: March 10, 1952
- Box: 80, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Foreman and Safety, 1953; Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Education and Personnel Department: "The Foreman and Safety", 1953; Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 28, 1953
- Box: 80, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Foreman and Safety: Instructor's Guide, 1953; Publication (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Box: 80, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Waste Reduction: Problems of Specialized Areas, 1953; Publication (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 24, 1953
- Box: 80, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Rules of the Central Safety Committee, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Box: 80, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Job Instructor Training: Lesson Plan for the Training Department Instructor, 1951; Publication (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Box: 80, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Job Instructor Training: Classroom Outline for the Training Department Instructor, Publication (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Box: 80, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employment Interviewing Workshop: Instructor's Lesson Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Box: 80, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Letter Explaining Variations in Company's Group Insrurance Plans, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)
    Author: Philip Marco
    Notes: March 11, 1952
- Box: 80, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: How Safe is Your Department? Are Your Employees?, Publication (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Departmental Safety Program: Instructor's Guide, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Box: 80, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Engineering Course: General Plan, Manufacturing Works, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 22, 1952
- Box: 80, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Farm Implement Division: 9/30/57 Letter to Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Author: C.W. Harter
  - Item 2: Farm Implement Division: 8-6-57 Letter to Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Author: Peter V. Moulder; C.W. Harter
  - Item 3: Farm Implement Division: 4-26-57 Letter to Employes, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Author: F.A. Graflund
  - Item 4: Farm Implement Division: Letter to Employees on Layoff, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Author: R.G. Mahal
    Notes: October 25, 1956
  - Item 5: Farm Implement Division: Letter to Employes on Memphis Works, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 24, 1956
  - Item 6: Farm Implement Division: 1-4-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Farm Implement Division: 12-8-54 Letter to Employes, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Farm Implement Division: 12-15-54 Letter to Employes, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Farm Implement Division: 3-18-55 Letter to Memphis Works Families, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Farm Implement Division: 2-18-55 Letter to Memphis Works Employes and their Families, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Farm Implement Division: 9-22-52 Letter to Employes, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Farm Implement Division: 7-25-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Farm Implement Division: 7-23-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Farm Implement Division: 6-8-56 Letter to Memphis Works Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Farm Implement Division: 12-21-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Farm Implement Division: 12-13-56 Letter to Employes, Wanted: A 1957 Safety Slogan, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Farm Implement Division: 8-5-57 Letter to Employes, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Farm Implement Division: 2-17-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Farm Implement Division: 12-8-54 Letter to Employes, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Farm Implement Division: 8-24-54 Letter to Employes, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: Farm Implement Division: 7-22-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: Farm Implement Division: 7-21-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: Farm Implement Division: 11-21-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Farm Implement Division: 12-21-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: Farm Implement Division: 12-21-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 26: Farm Implement Division: 11-15-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: Farm Implement Division: 4-22-55 Letter to Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 28: Farm Implement Division: 8-19-54 Letter to Employes, Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 29: Farm Implement Division: 1-24-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Item 30: Farm Implement Division: 1-23-56 Letter to Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Box: 80, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: International Harvester Company; Memphis Works: Letters to the Managerial Organization, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 14)
    Notes: July 27, 1955
  - Item 2: Memphis Works Christmas 1955 Letter to Employes, Publication (Box 80, Folder 14)
    Author: R.H. Mahal; C.W. Harter
- Box: 80, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: After-Hour Registration on Wide Range of Courses Given, Publication (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Box: 80, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin: 9-21-56, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Management Bulletin: 1-20-56, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Box: 80, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: 25 Plants and General Office, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Box: 80, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Program Survey: High School and College Courses, Publication (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Box: 80, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Christmas 1956 Letter to Employes, Publication (Box 80, Folder 19)
    Author: F.A. Graflund; R.G. Mahal; C.W. Harter
  - Item 2: Season's Greetings to all Supervisors, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 19)
    Author: C.W. Harter; R.G. Mahal; F.A. Graflund
  - Item 3: Merry Christmas and Happy New Year to all Employes, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Box: 80, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Memorandum, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 20)
    Notes: October 31, 1956
- Box: 80, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Inside Memphis Works, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Box: 80, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Physical Examination, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 22)
- Box: 80, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Application for Pension: Non-Salaried Permanently Incapacitated Employee, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 23)
- Box: 80, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Calculation of Disability Pension Benefits: Under Non-Contributory Pension Plan Agreement Between International Harvester Company and United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Calculation of Disability Pension Benefits: Under Non-Contributory Pension Plan Agreement Between International Harvester Company and Progressive Steel Workers Union, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 24)
- Box: 80, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Calculation of Disability Retirement Benefits Under the Contributory Annuity Plan as Agreed to Between Union and International Harvester Company, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Box: 80, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Amended Contributory Annuity Plan: Continuous Service Record of Retiring Employe, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 26)
- Box: 80, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Application for Disability Pension, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 27)
- Box: 80, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Status of Unions and Contracts, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 28)
- Box: 80, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Organization Chart, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 29)
- Box: 80, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Works Manager Organization Chart, 1952; Publication (Box 80, Folder 30)
- Box: 80, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Department: Work Performed by an Outside Contractor Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
    Author: W.J. Reilly
  - Item 2: Labor Relations Department: Allowance Rule of Paragraph 355, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Labor Relations Department: Company Improperly Refused to Discharge an Employe Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Labor Relations Department: Company Improperly Introduced a New Classification to Cover Inventory Taking Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Labor Relations Department: Press Operator was Entitled to a Handicap Allowance for Running his Press Under Irregular Conditions Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: Labor Relations Department: Company Properly Sent Employes Home After 4 Hours Work Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Labor Relations Department: Company Improperly Classified New York Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Labor Relations Department: Bargaining Unit Work was Improperly Being Performed by Excluded Personnel Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Labor Relations Department: Company Properly Discharged an Employe for Failure to Report for Work at the End of a Leave of Absence Case, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 31)
- Box: 80, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 318, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
    Author: David L. Cole
  - Item 2: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 314, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 313, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 317, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 316, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 315, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Permanent Arbitrator Decision Case No. 312, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 32)
- Box: 80, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: International Association of Machinists and International Harvester Company, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 33)
    Author: Willard H. Pedrick
    Notes: August 31, 1960
- Box: 80, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: For the Development of Technical, Professional and Managerial Personnel, 1958; Publication (Box 80, Folder 34)
- Box: 80, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Education and Personnel Department: Coordinated College Recruitment Procedures, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 35)
- Box: 80, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Flow Diagram of IH Coordinated College Recruitment, 1959; Publication (Box 80, Folder 36)
- Box: 80, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Notice of Hiring - College Recruitment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Notice of Position Vacancy - College Recruitment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 37)
- Box: 80, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Man Specification - College Recruitment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 38)
- Box: 80, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Termination Form, Publication (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 39)
- Box: 80, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Record of Screening Interview - College Recruitment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 40)
- Box: 80, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Film and Lesson Material on Materials Handling, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 41)
- Box: 80, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: 8 Principles of Materials Handling, Publication (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: In-Process Materials Handling: Instructor's Guide, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 42)
- Box: 80, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan - Managerial Employes - All U.S. Operations, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 43)
    Author: Ivan L. Willis
- Box: 80, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: A President's Problems in Labor Relations, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 44)
    Author: John L. McCaffrey
- Box: 80, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report of Manufacturing Training, 1954; Publication (Box 80, Folder 45)
    Author: E.H. Reed
- Box: 80, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Status of Unions and Contracts, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 46)
- Box: 80, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: A Practical Plan for Executive Development, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 47)
    Notes: February 16, 1956
- Box: 80, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Man or MousePile Material Safety: Use Proper BlockingNever Exceed a Safe Height, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 48)
- Box: 80, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Your Contributory Annuity Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 80, Folder 49)
- Box: 80, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: The Presidents' Forum: How to Make a Managera la Inland Steel, 1963; Publication (Box 80, Folder 50)
    Author: John F. Smith, Jr.
- Box: 80, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Process of Managing: Branch Office Management Development Program, 1978; Publication (Box 80, Folder 51)
- Box: 80, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: His Future is in The Making, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 52)
- Box: 80, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Graduate Program in Engineering and Physics: College of Engineering, 1960; Publication (Box 80, Folder 53)
- Box: 80, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 80, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: General Education Program: IBM Department of Education, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 54)
- Box: 80, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Electronic Technician Training, 1956; Publication (Box 80, Folder 55)
- Box: 80, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: General Education Program: IBM School, 1951; Publication (Box 80, Folder 56)
- Box: 80, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Engineer Training Program: Commercial Products Engineering Laboratory, 1957; Publication (Box 80, Folder 57)
- Box: 80, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 80, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Communication Process and Techniques: Branch Office Management Development Program, 1978; Publication (Box 80, Folder 58)
- Box: 80, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 80, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: IBM Safety Manual, 1966; Publication (Box 80, Folder 59)
- Box: 80, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Vital to Victory: Safety Rules for Machine Shop, Publication (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - Item 2: Cafeteria Safety Manual, 1967; Publication (Box 80, Folder 60)
- Box: 80, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 80, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration: Opportunity, Security, Protection, Publication (Box 80, Folder 61)